doctoruna.com 2015-09-30

# Privacy Policy | DoctorUna - UAE

**1\. Introduction**

DoctorUna FZ-LLC (“us,” “we” or “DoctorUna”) is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, visitors, and other users of the DoctorUna services (“Services”) provided via the DoctorUna website (collectively, "Site") . Our goal is to provide you with a secure online experience and to ensure that any information you submit to us is private and used/disclosed only for the purposes and in the means described below.

This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site or any website of DoctorUna's partners, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site is governed by this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use. If you are registering an account or using the Site on behalf of an individual or entity other than yourself, you represent that you are authorized by such individual or entity to accept this Privacy Policy on such individual's or entity's behalf.

As a doctor/dentist search site, DoctorUna will ask practitioners to submit any information relevant to the patients search in order to conduct/optimize the search functionality. All information is submitted exclusively on a voluntary basis. Please find below details of our member privacy practices.

 **2\. Traffic Data Collected**

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Site; (4) types of web browsers used to access the Site; (5) referring source which may have sent you to the Site; and (6) other information associated with the interaction of your browser and the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”).

 **3\. Registration & Personal Information Collected**

To fully participate in our doctor/dentist search activities, we require you to register as a DoctorUna member. Non-registered users are granted partial participation access eg. non-registered patients may view profiles and availability but will not be able to book appointments.

To register, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your e-mail address, phone number and DoctorUna password); (2) Demographic Data (such as your gender, your date of birth and your address); (3) Insurance Data (such as your insurance carrier and insurance plan); and (4) Medical Data (such as your previous doctors and dentists (“Providers”) visited, your reason for visit and your date of visit, your medical history, and other medical and protected health information you choose to share with us). If you communicate with us by, for example, e-mail or letter, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

Doctors and dentists will need to create a DoctorUna Public Profile and they fully understand that by opting to do so their profile becomes in the public domain and can be accessed by search engines. Doctors and dentists need to bear in mind that once a Public Profile gets activated, search engines and others may obtain permanent copies of it and even if the user disables their profile, DoctorUna cannot restrict views of the copies of the Public Profile obtained by these search engines and other crawlers.

 **4\. Your Profile Log In**

Registered doctors/dentists and patients have access to a personal profile log in from where they can manage their appointments. All information in this space can only be viewed by the registered user(s) and accessed after logging in with your password.

DoctorUna is the sole owner of information collected on the registration pages and we will not disclose this information to anyone outside of DoctorUna. Your contact information (such as name and email address may however be used to contact you about any features/services on our site which we believe may be of interest.

 **5\. Interactive and Installed Tools**

We also collect other information, some of which may be Personal Information that you voluntarily provide to us when you choose to use some of the Site’s interactive tools and services (“Interactive Tools”), such as searching for Providers, searching for available appointments with them, and completing medical history forms ("Medical History Forms") prior to appointments. We also collect information you provide voluntarily in free-form text boxes on the Site and through responses to surveys, questionnaires and the like. Some of the free Interactive Tools on our Site ask you for health-related Personal Information. You may elect to use certain Services available through the Site that require you to download and install software on your computer (“Installed Tools”). The Installed Tools may collect and transmit information from your computer system solely relating to use of the Installed Tools and for the purpose of providing you the relevant Services, for example, by informing DoctorUna when a user is logged on and available to receive update or alert notices.

 **6\. Cookies**

“Cookies” are small computer files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive that contain information such as user ID, user preferences, lists of pages visited and activities conducted while browsing the Site. At your option, expense and responsibility, you may block cookies or delete cookies from your hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, you may not have access to the entire set of features of the Site.

Generally, we use “cookies” to customize your experience on our Site and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site.

In addition, our business partners may use cookies to provide us with anonymous data and information regarding the use of our Site. Specifically, some of our business partners use cookies to show DoctorUna ads on other sites on the internet as a result of you using the Site. Such cookies do not contain any Personal Information. 

Other cookies used by our business partners may collect other non-personally identifying information, such as the computer’s IP address, type of operating system, type of internet browsing software, what web pages were viewed at what time, the geographic location of your internet service provider and demographic information, such as gender and age range. This information is used to provide DoctorUna with more information about our users’ demographics and internet behaviors. You may find out more about the information collected and how to opt-out of receiving these cookies by visiting our partners website. We do not link the information stored in these cookies directly to any of your Personal Information you submit while on the Site, however.

 **7\. Web Beacons**

In limited circumstances we also may use “Web Beacons” to collect anonymous, non-personal information about your use of our Site and the sites of selected sponsors and advertisers, and your use of emails, special promotions or newsletters we send to you. “Web Beacons” are tiny graphic image files imbedded in a web page or email that provide a presence on the web page or email and send back to its home server information from the user’s browser. The information collected by web beacons allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using the Site and selected sponsors' and advertisers' sites, or opening our emails, and for what purposes.

 **8\. Storage**

We store all Traffic Data and review postings indefinitely, even after “deletion,” and may archive such information elsewhere. We store all Personal Information until you request that we modify or delete it, in which case we may still end up retaining some of that information.

 **9\. DoctorUna’s Use of Your Information**

We may use your Personal Information to recommend certain resources or medical providers. We may use your Contact Data to send you information about DoctorUna or our products or Services, to contact you when necessary, including to remind you of upcoming or follow-up appointments, and in conjunction with your use of certain Interactive Tools. We may use your Demographic Data, your Traffic Data, your Insurance Data or your Medical Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Site, in emails and in other communications, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences. You agree that DoctorUna may use Personal Information to allow your doctors to make appointments with other doctors on your behalf through the Services. We may also use your de-identified Personal Information to run (or authorize third parties to run) statistical research on individual or aggregate health or medical trends. Such research would only use your Personal Information in an anonymous manner that cannot be tied directly back to you.

 **10\. User Choice**

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information.

 **11\. Confidentiality and Security**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless we believe in good faith that disclosure of your Personal Information or any other information we collect about you is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order or other legal process; (2) protect the rights, property or safety of DoctorUna or another party; (3) enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use; or (4) respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties.

 **12\. Public Information**

Any information that you may reveal in a review posting or other online discussion or forum is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before disclosing any personally identifiable information in any public forum. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.

 **13.Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. For example, when you enter sensitive information on our Site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Although we make good faith efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, you should understand that there is no such thing as complete security, and we do not guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of your Personal Information. If we become aware that your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the nature and extent of the disclosure (to the extent we know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law.

 **14\. Lost or Stolen Information**

You must promptly notify us if your Contact Data is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that Contact Data from your account and update our records accordingly.

 **15\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy so please review it frequently. If we do, then we will notify you here, as well as by posting a notice on our Site and, where appropriate, a link to the modified policy so that you can review it. In all cases, use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

 **16\. Controlling Your Personal Information**

As a registered user of the Site, you can modify some of the Personal Information you have included in your profile or change your username by logging in and accessing your account. Upon your request, DoctorUna will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete your account and the Personal Information in your profile; however, it may be impossible to remove your account without some residual information being retained by DoctorUna. DoctorUna has no obligation to delete any data or information you provide on a Medical History Form following termination of your account or the account of any medical professional to whom your Medical History Form was submitted through the Site. 

**17\. Links to Other Websites**

The Site contains links to third party websites to which DoctorUna has no affiliation. DoctorUna does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. Some web sites may have the look and feel of our Site. Please be aware that you may be on a different site and that this Privacy Policy only covers our Site. Should you decide to visit one of these third party websites, we suggest that you read its privacy policy.
